League of Women Voters of Saratoga County; Records apap339
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Project and Subject Files, 1968-2015; 3; 1.92 cubic ft.
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Charleston and Galway, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Clifton Park and Halfmoon, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Greenfield, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Instrument and Training, 2006; Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Malta, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Milton, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Northumberland, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Retroactive Contract, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Saratoga Springs, 2003-2004; Undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Saratoga Springs and Wilton, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Stillwater, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Surveys and Results, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Training Materials, 2006; Undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Racial Profiling Consensus Report, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Roohan, Margaret - Obituary, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Russian Delegation - AED Program, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Russian Delegation - Arrangements for Community Visits, 2004; Undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Russian Delegation - Budget and Acceptance, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Russian Delegation - Budget, Arrangement, Expense Report, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Russian Delegation - Communications, 2002; Undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Russian Delegation - Communications, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Russian Delegation - Community Profile, 2002; Undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Russian Delegation - Cultural Orientation Handbook, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Russian Delegation - Final Report and Schedules, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Russian Delegation - Final Report and Schedules, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Russian Delegation - Forms, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Russian Delegation - Gifts, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Russian Delegation - Host Packet, 2002; Undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Russian Delegation - News Clippings, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Russian Delegation - News Clippings, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Russian Delegation -New York Times Booklet, ca. 2004 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Russian Delegation - Nuclear Controversy, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Russian Delegation - Open World Information, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Russian Delegation - Participant Profiles, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Russian Delegation - Participant Profiles, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Russian Delegation - Photographs, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Russian Delegation - Photographs, 2004 (Cd 9)
  - Russian Delegation - Photographs, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Russian Delegation - Photo Negatives, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Russian Delegation - Photo Negatives, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Russian Delegation - Services Arranged, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Russian Delegation - Sheelagh Bailys Photographs, 2004 October 30 (Cd 10)
  - Russian Delegation - Translators, 2002; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Russian Delegation - Translators, ca. 2004 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Russian Delegation Visit, 2004 (Video-tape 13)
  - Saratoga County Health Department Consensus, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Saratoga Springs City Charter Activity, 1965; 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Saratoga Springs City Charter Activity, 1974-1976; 1979; Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Saratoga Springs City Charter Activity, 1983-1985; 1991; Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Saratoga Springs City Charter Local Law Amendments, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Saratoga Springs City Charter Review, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Saratoga Springs City Charter Text, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Saratoga Springs City Charter, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Seneca Falls, 2013 (Cd 11)
  - Sojourner Truth, 2014 (Dvd 7)
  - Student Voters Articles, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Student Voting Rights - Court Cast Establishing, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Student Voting Rights - LWV Information, 1998; 2003; Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Student Voting Rights - Skidmore Court Case, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Student Voting Rights - Skidmore Polling Site Problems, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Sunshine Week - Grant Application and Final Report, 2005-2006; Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Sunshine Week - News Clippings, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Sunshine Week - Openness in Government Forums, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Sunshine Week - Sample Packet, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Tribute to Barbara Thomas on Her Retirement, ca. 2011 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Trip to Val-kill, 2014 (Cd 12)
  - Voting Machine Lobby Packet, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Voter's Services, Candidate Responses, 1973-1975; 1977; 1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Water Study, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Clippings and Scrapbooks, 1969-2010; Undated; 4; .69 cubic ft.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  The Clippings and Scrapbook Series consists of various newspaper clippings detailing and highlighting the activism of and events hosted by the League of Women Voters of Saratoga County. These files also include photographs of candidates and events, event bulletins, and flyers. There also are a few objects, including a tote bag and fan. The scrapbooks were originally created by the Saratoga Springs Public Library. Archivists unbound them for preservation purposes.
  - Clippings SB, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clippings SB, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Clippings SB, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Clippings SB, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clippings SB, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Clippings SB, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Clippings: Voter's Guide, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Clippings SB, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Clippings SB, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Clippings SB, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Clippings SB, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Clippings SB, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Clippings SB, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Clippings SB, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Clippings SB, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Clippings SB, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Clippings SB, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Clippings SB, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Clippings SB, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Clippings SB, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Clippings SB, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Clippings SB, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Clippings SB, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Clippings SB, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Clippings SB, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Clippings SB, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Clippings SB, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Clippings SB, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Clippings SB, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Clippings SB, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Clippings SB, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Clippings SB, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Clippings SB, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Clippings SB, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Clippings SB, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Clippings SB, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Clippings SB, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Clippings SB, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Clippings SB, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Clippings SB, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Tote Bag About Electronic Voting, Undated (Oversized 1)